A Guide to the Papers of the Wednesday Music Club, 1932-1978
Special Collections Department, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Wednesday Music Club 1932-1978
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
6875-b
This collection consists of 5 boxes.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited on 1980 December 11.
Scope and Content Information
Club established to share musical culture with persons of similar interests and provide opportunities to perform. The papers contain constitution and by-laws, minute books, publicity records and releases, yearbooks, check registers, correspondence regarding scholarships and club activities, letters and drawings from elementary school children, programs, and clippings.
Contents List
- Scholarship Correspondence 1959-1968 (Box 1)
- Material Regarding Club Activities and Programs 1949-1953, n.d. (Box 1)
- Publicity Releases 1975-1979 (Box 1)
- George Rogers Clark Elementary School, Letters to Mrs. Little and Mrs. Perguson 1977 Feb. 15-17 (Box 1)
- George Rogers Clark Elementary School, Letters to Mrs. Little and Mrs. Perguson 1977 Feb 17 (Box 1)
- Meriwether Lewis Elementary School, Letters to Mrs. Little and Mrs. Perguson 1977 Feb 18 (Box 1)
- Meriwether Lewis Elementary School, Drawings to Mrs. Little and Mrs. Perguson n.d. (Box 1)
- Yearbooks 1957-1971, 1976-1977 (Box 1)
- Check Registers 1969-1978 (Box 1)
- Minute Book ca. 1932-1942 (Box 2)
- Minute Book 1942 Jun-1954 Jan (Box 2)
- Minute Book 1954 Feb-1962 Jun (Box 2)
- Minute Book 1962 Sep-1972 May (Box 3)
- Minute Book 1972 Sep-1976 May (Box 3)
- Minute Book 1976 Jun-1978 May (Box 4)
- Publicity Records 1959-1967 (Box 4)
- Publicity Records 1968-1973 (Box 4)
- Publicity Records 1974 (Box 4)
- Programs 1953-1957 (Box 5)
- Newspaper Clippings 1960-1968 (Box 5)